Trench 11 is a horror, thriller, war film directed by Leo Scherman.
In the final days of WWI a shell-shocked soldier must lead a mission deep beneath the
trenches to stop a German plot that could turn the tide of the war.
Lt. Berton, played by Rossif Sutherland.
Reiner, played by Robert Stadlober.
Dr. Priest, played by Charlie Carrick.
Kaptain Mueller, played by Shaun Benson.
Major Jennings, played by Ted Atherton.
Captain Cooper, played by Luke Humphrey.
Trench 11 is a 2017 Canadian horror thriller film directed by Leo Scherman.
The movie stars Rossif Sutherland, Robert Stadlober, Charlie Carrick, Shaun Benson, Ted
Atherton, Luke Humphrey, Jeff Strome, Adam Hurtig, and Karine Vanasse.
The setting takes place near the end of the First World War where a group of Allied soldiers are sent
to investigate a secret German bunker and discover the horrors that lay beneath it.
The film's development began in 2011 with its filming
beginning in late 2016 in Winnipeg, Canada.
The film explores themes of biological weapon,
france, world war i, bunker, infection.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.